cuponation.com.sg 2014-11-22

# Cuponation Privacy Policy - Best coupons and deals of top Singapore retailers

PRIVACY POLICY

Please read the following Privacy Policy carefully since your use of the www.cuponation.com.sg website and its services signifies your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy, in whole or part, you should not use this website or services of CupoNation.

The website www.cuponation.com.sg (“the website”, “website”) is operated by CupoNation GmbH ("CupoNation ", "we," "us," "our") is committed to protect your (“Customer”, “User”, “You”) privacy and will only use information that has been collected from you in a lawful manner in full accordance with data protection laws applicable in Singapore. While from our end we will try our best to ensure that the data collected by us is accurate and updated, you can check the information and inform us regarding any changes required and we will correct the same within a reasonable amount of time. The website and its services are intended for users above the age of 18 years. 

In addition, CupoNation also provides additional services through CupoNotifier, a browser extension (“browser addon”) which is also operated by Cuponation GmbH. The stated privacy policy in this document affects CupoNotifier in the same matter as it does to CupoNation.

CupoNotifier is designed to inform you about coupons and deals from selected online retailers while browsing online. CupoNotifier works as following: (1st) When you visit a websites of an affiliate retailer that is part of our program, CupoNotifier is engineered to recognize the website and determine if there are coupons or deals available. (2nd) Should there be coupons or deals available that the CupoNotifier recognizes, it will show a panel with the coupons unless the affiliate retailer has informed CupoNation not to do so for their website. (3rd) If you were to click on a coupon or deal, by default this will redirect you to the site where the deals are located and cookies will be added to your computer. You can find more information on cookies under the section “Using tools and cookies”.

Information collected by CupoNation:

In order to inform you of the best existing offers while you are shopping online, we collect different types of information: non-personal information and personal information (which is collected when actively and voluntarily provided by you).

In order for CupoNotifier to serve its purpose, it processes among other the following data: browser version and type, time of software usage, websites on which software is used, anonymized software ID. All information that CupoNotifier deals with will be treated as stated under the section “Using this information” under the Privacy Policy.

An Internet Protocol ("IP") address is a unique identifier that certain electronic devices use to identify and communicate with each other on the Internet. When you visit the website, we may view the IP address of the device you use to connect to the Internet. The IP could also be viewed upon installation and usage of our browser extension CupoNotifier. We use this information to determine the location of the device and understand from what regions of the world our website visitors are originating and adopt our localized service to the location.

All information collected by us is stored in accordance with relevant data protection laws in Singapore.

 Using this information:

 The information that we collect is used to:

Provide you with regular information about CupoNation, including marketing literature.

To facilitate services that are provided on the website or the CupoNotifier addon.

To contact you for information and/ or services that you may have requested from us.

To improve our website based on information received by you.

Create a personalized experience for you based upon your past visits to our website.

 This information is used for the aforementioned uses by CupoNation, CupoNation group companies and our agents and subcontractors.

 In case you opt-in for our newsletters, we will send you our newsletters and other marketing/promotional materials and may ask you for feedback on our services.  However, you may choose to opt out of such newsletters at any point in the future by unsubscribing from our newsletters.

If we do receive your personal information, we will only use it for the purposes described in this policy, and will not disclose the gathered information outside of Cuponation GmbH (CupoNation and CupoNotifier) unless (a) it is necessary in connection with a sale of all or substantially all of the assets of Cuponation GmbH or the merger of Cuponation GmbH into another entity or any consolidation, share exchange, combination, reorganization, or like transaction in which Cuponation GmbH is not the survivor, (b) you authorize us to do so, or (c) otherwise as we are required or permitted by law.

If you do not agree to our “Using this information” policy above, you cannot use our website or the CupoNotifier browser extension. Your continued use of our website and CupoNotifier browser extension constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

Using tools and cookies:

On our website and within our browser extension CupoNotifier, we use "cookies". Cuponation GmbH uses cookie technology to understand general information on site traffic trends such as most frequently visited pages or our affiliate retailer’s online stores. This information is usually captured as aggregate information and is not specific to individual users, which enables us to improve the content, user flow and functionality of our webpage. “Cookie” elements help us identify your computer, but maintain your personal information anonymous. Your web browser can be set to refuse cookies. Nevertheless, if you are not accepting “cookies”, functionalities may not be displayed and some of our services could be out of your access both on our webpage and on the CupoNotifier browser extension.

Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Ireland Limited (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies” to help us analyse how the site is used. The anonymized information generated by those cookies about the customers use of this website and current IP will be transmitted anonymized by your browser to be stored by Google on servers in the United States and other countries. Google will use this information on our behalf for the purpose of evaluating the aggregated usage of our website, compiling reports on website activity and providing other services related to website activity and internet usage to us. The IP address collected through Google Analytics will not be associated with any other data held by Google. You may choose not to opt-in to permit use of the google cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. You may also stop the transmission of information generated by the cookies about your use of this website and of your IP address to Google, by downloading and installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser addon available here: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout 

Security:

CupoNation undertakes multiple security measures to ensure the protection of the information that you provide to us. As for data transmitted between the website and/or users, we may be unable to avert unauthorized access by third parties during transit. You acknowledge, however, that no transmission of data over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, despite our efforts. Thus, while we will use commercially reasonable means possible to ensure the security of information you transmit to us, we cannot guarantee that such information will not be intercepted by third parties.

Rules and regualtions:

Cuponation GmbH and the services provided by the company through CupoNation and CupoNotifier store all data and information in servers in Ireland, Singapore and Brazil where the pertinent data protection laws apply. The information however is managed by Cuponation GmbH in Germany where the company is legally established as an entity.

Links to other Websites

We may provide links to other websites that we do not control, these include those of our affiliate partners’ online stores. We do not assume responsibility for the privacy practices, products, services or any other content of any websites or pages that is not under our control. Cuponation GmbH does not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third-party websites. Moreover, Cuponation GmbH disclaims all responsibility for the subsequent use of an email address or any other personally identifiable information you have provided to an affiliate store or any other website we might link to that is not under our control.

CupoNation/CupoNotifier users should be aware, that content presented to them through their use of CupoNation/CupoNotifier may include but is not limited to targeted advertisements and other sponsored content. This content displayed as a result of CupoNation/CupoNotifier, may be protected by intellectual property rights which are owned by the sponsors or advertisers who provide that content to or for the use of CupoNation/CupoNotifier (or by other persons or companies on their behalf). You may not modify, rent, lease, loan, sell, distribute or create derivative works based on this content (either in whole or in part) unless you have been specifically told that you may do so by the licensor or the owners of that content, in a separate agreement.  
  
Facebook Sign up:

Your user data may be transmitted to a 3rd party service for the purposes of collection only. Your email will not be used for marketing purposes for any third party not directly related to Cuponation Gmbh.

Facebook login:  We allow users to connect to our platform via Facebook Connect, and store data related to their Facebook account in Cuponation Gmbh systems.  This data can only be used by Cuponation to deliver a more customised offering to users. Any information collected in this manner will not be transmitted to any third parties. Cuponation Gmbh is not responsible for any user information stored by Facebook. Users may disconnect from Cuponation in the Facebook user settings.

Changes to our Privacy Policy:

CupoNation reserves the rights to amend this Privacy Policy, in part or whole, at any time and from time to time. Any such changes will be effective immediately and will be reflected on the website and communicated to users though reasonable means.

The most recent version of the policy is reflected by the version date located at the bottom of this Policy. Since this policy can be subject to change we encourage users to check it every once in a while, as your continued use will mean that you accept the modified terms. The privacy policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal right in or on behalf of any party.

By using our Website and CupoNotifier addon, you agree that you have read, understood and agreed with our Privacy Policy in its entirety, and consent to be bound by it.

Customer Service

In case of any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please reach out to us at contact@cuponation.com

 Date 09/08/2013
